-真的吗  -对的
- Wow, really? - Oh, yeah. Yeah.
-那里基本上乱成一锅粥了  -是吗
- It's a shit show over there apparently. - Yeah?
对 广告主们一哄而散
Yeah. Like, advertisers bailing,
据说我爸也下台了
my dad is out of it, by all accounts.
现在是格丽·吉尔曼掌权
You know, Gerri Kellman in charge?
恕我直言 格丽虽然挺不错的
Sorry. I mean, Gerri's great,
我其实很喜欢格丽
I actually I actually love Gerri, you know,
但她就是个墙头草 不胜其任
but Gerri is a time server who's way out of her depth.
同时 好的方面是
Meanwhile, on the upside,
司法部已经在和我交涉免责协议了
the DOJ and I are in contact about the terms of my immunity deal.
所以 形势对他们非常不利
So yeah. Does not look good for them.
好的
Right.
这些都仅供参考
All that's on background,
毕竟 很多事情瞬息万变
you know, as we said a lot of moving parts.
总之... 我们正式开始吧
But.. but, yeah, please, let's dive in.
我可以录音的 对吧
So you're okay if I record this, right?
当然 不用问我 完全没问题
Yeah. Hey, am I okay? I am I am great.
-太棒了 谢谢  -录吧 我绝对坦诚
- Great. Thank you. - Let's record. Open the kimono.
谢谢
Thank you.
这会写进报道吗
So will this be in the piece?
"肯德尔·罗伊点了份茴香沙拉
"Kendall Roy ordered a shaved
磨磨蹭蹭地品尝 显得有些过分好奇"
fennel salad and picked at it, inquisitively?"
你挺在乎自己的形象嘛
You're quite concerned with how you're gonna come across.
不会 还好
Not really. No.
有吗 我来自一个形象至上的世界
Am I? No, look, I come from a world of image,
那是我的家族企业
that's the family business.
你看过索菲·伊沃比的独角戏了吗
I mean, did you see the Sophie Iwobi monologue?
[影射俄狄浦斯 希腊神话中杀父娶母的悲剧人物]
她搞了个段子 说我是"俄狄孬种"
Yeah. Well, she did a bit "Oedipussy"?
很幽默 对吧 但根本不痛不痒
It's funny, right? But, you know, it doesn't hurt now because,
因为 我知道我是谁
because I am who I am.
而且 我想插上一面旗
And, and, and I wanna plant a flag,
真正进入公司内部 然后插上一面旗
I wanna physically get in and plant a flag,
就插在我家族企业里
you know, for that inside my family's business.
关于你的家族企业
And in terms of your family business,
人们确实对于你们兄妹有一些疑问
one question that people do have is about your siblings.
他们的立场是什么
So where are they in this?
你有跟他们保持密切联系吗
Have you managed to stay close with them?
有 当然了
You know, sure. Absolutely.
有一些问题 但是
There, there are issues, but, uh
基本上 还不错
essentially, yeah.
我目前的心态很积极
I'm just really happy in my headspace.
我希望他们也是
And I hope they're happy in theirs.
继   承   之   战
第 3 季  第 3 集
你好啊 总裁
Hey. El Presidente.
你心态怎么样 很积极吗
How's your headspace? You happy in it?
还行吧 你喜欢报道的结尾吗
Uh, yeah. You like the ending?
"我爱我的孩子们 他们叫什么来着
"Oh, I love my kids, what are their names again?"
模糊脸和谁在乎吗"
"Blur Face and Who Cares?"
-好了  -对了 可以推进那笔买卖了
- All right. - Oh. And let's press go on that sale,
以色列的机器学习项目
the Israeli machine learning operation.
-这个嘛  -怎么了
- Okay?  - What?
没什么... 好的 我会去处理
What... nothing. Good. Let me get into that.
-看着我  -我在看啊
- Look at me. - No, I am.
-我看着你呢  -各就各位
- Hi. I see you. - Action stations.
要开战略会议了 该去给老爸的蛋蛋挠痒痒了
Strategy meet. Time to go tickle my dad's balls.
-好  -你好 卡洛丽娜
- Yeah. - Hi, Karolina.
希望我们的代理执行官没有太入戏
I just hope our acting CEO isn't getting too fucking acting.
我们应该重新讲述皮诺曹 当恐怖故事讲
I'll tell you what's a scary story we should maybe reboot. Pinocchio.
活过来的提线木偶
A puppet that comes to life.
够了 我们开始吧
Oh, come on. Let's get started.
让他们自己跟上
They can catch up.
老爸 你心态如何
Hey, Dad. How's your headspace?
我听说格丽在关注以色列那事
I hear Gerri's looking at the Israeli outfit.
那不是很重要
Uh, pretty insignificant.
不 不 不 我心里对那事的前景有数
No, no, no, no, no, no. I have a shape of things in mind for that.
就是串流播放什么的
GoJo Go, I don't know, streaming.
终止那项计划 砍掉它
No. Kill it, okay? Just kill it.
怎么了 你不确定该听谁的吗
What? What? Are you checking the chain of command?
不是的
No.
他说"插旗子"是什么意思
What does he mean by "Plant a flag", huh?
拜托 别他妈在我边上晃
Please, don't fucking hover.
有消息称 肯德尔打算进公司
Um, there's talk that, uh, Kendall's planning to come in.
开什么天大的玩笑
You're fucking kidding?
进来这里吗
In here?
那个叛徒胆敢踏进这栋楼一步
That rat steps one foot inside this building,
我就打断他的鼻梁
I'll punch him in the nose, okay?
那的确是个大家都满意的成年人的解决方案
Well, I think that's the grown-up solution that keeps everyone happy.
去搞明白这混蛋想干嘛
Find out what this fucker's planning.
我现在不想看到这家伙捣乱
I don't need him in my teeth right now.
我可以去探个底
I can I can scope that out.
我可以在今晚的新闻晚宴上逮到他
I can catch him tonight, if you'd like, at the journalism dinner.
但我们该拿什么跟他争呢
But, you know, what are we doing to counter?
对 没错 你们都该出面制止他
Yes. Yes! You should all be out there, call him out on this.
我们不是讨论过要办员工大会吗
well, we did discuss the town hall event?
我认同 可以凝聚人心
Yeah. I like it. It brings everyone together.
-对  -员工可以匿名发问 面对面交流
- Yeah. - Open, anonymous questions. Employee facing.
如果关乎改革 我愿意主持
Yeah. I'm happy to lead it, if it's about change.
是吗 看现在是谁在"插旗子"了
Oh, you are? Now who's planting a flag?
若要先发制人
In terms of getting proactive,
雨果让弗兰克顿拟定了一些整版的声明稿
Hugo had Frankton's put together some full-page responses.
对 有几个不错的
Yeah. There were a there were a couple we liked.
整个版面 搭配一些承诺
Full-page, with, a number of pledges,
具体措辞可以再调整
we can figure out the verbiage.
标语是"我们懂"
And the tagline "We Get It."
我觉得挺潮的
I thought it was quite funky.
"我们懂" 邮轮上的女士们也懂了吗
"We get it." A bit like those ladies on the cruise ship got it?
-格丽也觉得不错  -对 真的有点像
- Gerri liked it? - Yeah, it's a little,
"好了 我们懂了 别再逼逼那些强奸案了"
"Yeah, yeah, we get it already, stop moaning about the rapes."
洛根 调查员来电询问
Logan, um, we have agents on the phone,
韦斯达是否接受他们发送文件传票
asking if Waystar's willing to accept service of a document subpoena?
-叫他们滚蛋  -好吧
- Tell them to fuck off. - Oh, okay.
-凯莉 等下 他在开玩笑  -爸
- Kerry, hang on, he's kidding. - Dad?
洛根 我在想咱们可能要想想多久开始合作了
Logan, I'm just wondering, uh, when we might start to play ball.
意思是 所有人都得配合
I mean, everybody cooperates.
也许我不想呢
Maybe I don't do that dance.
那股东大会上的人会作何感想呢
And how does that feel in regards to the shareholder meeting?
如果我们不接受
We don't accept service, in an hour,
一小时内就会有两个调查员直接找上门
there's gonna be two agents here to serve you,
与此同时 他们可以强制传唤你去面对大陪审团
and while they're at it, they could subpoena you to the grand jury.
去他们的
Fuck 'em.
-洛根  -叫他们滚蛋
- Logan? - Tell 'em to fuck off!
联邦调查局 举起手来
FBI, hands up!
-你还好吗  -格雷格 说实话不太好
- How's it going? - To be honest? Not great, Greg.
调查情况不太乐观
It's looking pretty bad with the investigation, and, um,
洛根让我们把这个吃了
Logan says we have to take these.
氰化物[剧毒] 整个团队都得吃
Cyanide pills. The whole team.
只是薄荷糖 傻蛋 来一个吧 你有口臭
It's a mint, you doofus. Take one. Your breath really does stink.
我带你看个东西
Hey, can I show you something?
-好  -来吧
- Yeah. - Come on.
格雷戈里 我的参谋长
Gregory, my chief of staff,
泛美网科的长腿小王子 你值得一个新办公室
leggy princeling of ATN, you deserve a new office.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
这里 好像不是很好
I mean, it's, it's not very nice.
太失礼了 这是你的新家
That's rude, rude boy. It's your new place.
我懂了 这是个惩罚对吧
Okay. I see this is punishment, right?
是因为我没用公司的律师对吧
This is because I'm not taking the company lawyer, right?
然后我现在要被降职了吗
And I am I getting demoted right now?
在调查中给你降职吗
In the middle of an investigation?
不 不 这只是
No. No. This is just part
办公室改革的标准流程
of a totally standard office rationalization.
真的 做你想做的就好
No. No, no, no. You do whatever you like, you know.
和肯德尔乱搞 自己请律师
Hang out with Kendall. Take your own counsel.
听说你的律师很不错啊
I hear you have a really great lawyer.
听说你随时随地都能找到他 是吗
Is it true you can find him anytime day or night?
-是的  -因为他有那种
- Yes. - Because he has one of those bowties
-可以旋转发光的绅士领结吗  -他真的很不错
- that lights up and spins around? - He's actually really good.
我对他很满意
I'm very, very happy with him.
哥们 我说句老实话
Listen, on the level, buddy,
绝不骗你 现在有无数把刀正在打磨
On the level, there are a million knives being sharpened right now.
司法部会像鸡巴麦田里的联合收割机一样
The DOJ's gonna be like a combine harvester in a wheat field of dicks, okay?
所以我理解 我明白这很难
So I understand, I get it. I see that this is tough.
我选了韦斯达 我认为这一步最稳妥
I have gone Waystar, I think that's safest.
但今晚 我要拜访一个朋友
But tonight, I'm actually seeing
听听一些就我状况的客观建议
a pal to get an objective take on my situation.
如果你愿意的话 可以加入
And if you want, if you want, I can fold you in.
-今晚吗  -对 我只是想
- Tonight? - Yeah. I just thought, you know,
喝杯啤酒放松放松 回顾下过去
over a beer, we could kick back and recall what happened,
并且确保我们的回忆完全一致
and make sure that we remember it exactly the same way.
-什么  -不 只是肯
- What? - No. It's just Ken.
-让肯滚  -好 让他滚
- Fuck Ken. - Yeah. No, fuck Ken,
-他不是问题 但...  -但什么
- a hundred percent,but... - But what?
他... 这很愚蠢
He's... it's stupid,
他今晚要送我一块表作为感谢
he's giving me a watch tonight to say thanks,
所以 我不知道 我...
um, for so, I don't know, I...
你把自己卖了就为一块表吗
You sold your ass for a watch?
表我给你买 傻蛋 晚上来就完事儿了
I'll buy you a watch, dickwad. Just fucking come over!
好的 我会想办法的 我想来
Okay. I'll try to come. I wanna come.
待着
Stay.
你爸爸只是想知道
You know, your dad just wondered,
既然大众对他的看法有些片面...
since the public discourse about your father feels really one-sided...
是的 我们希望你们能帮我们拓展更多维度
Yes. We would love your help getting more dimensions.
这会是一场完全可控的商业访谈
It would be totally controlled business interview,
最后会有些轻松环节
with some softballs at the end.
是的 比如小西 或者类似你的人
Yeah. So Shiv, or someone like Shiv,
分享一些关于你爸的回忆和感情
sharing some memories and feelings about your dad.
好的 我明白
Yeah, I see. I think I
但我是策反肯德尔的最好人选
think I'm best placed neutralizing Kendall.
好把 那就选个类似你的人
Okay. Well, you or someone like you.
好吧 行 去他妈的
All right. Yeah, fine. Fuck you.
我会跟我爸公开表白
I'll go out and I say I love Dad.
为什么不呢 我当然爱他 去你的
Why not? I do. So yeah, fuck you.
看看你 高中最帅的拉拉队长
Aww, look at you. Cutest cheerleader in high school.
你真的让田径队的人帮你指交 来赚午餐钱吗
Is it true you let the track team finger bang you for lunch money?
-别把你自己的回忆套在我身上  -好的
- Stop projecting your memories onto me. - All right.
我喜欢这个 重量刚好 我...
I like it. I like it. It's a good weight, I...
肯 就问一下
Ken? Real quick, can you,
你要不就把这个借给我算了
can you just give me the green light on this?
它太贵了 我通常都用手机看时间
It's very expensive. I mean, I usually just use my phone for all my time needs.
没事 管他呢 哥们 你值得拥有
Yeah. Fuck it. Fuck it, man, you deserve it.
手机就是个小玩意儿 像纽扣
Dude, your phone is a widget, a button.
全美的清洁工都人手一个
Every janitor in America has one.
而你的手表可是吊炸天的蒙娜丽莎
Your watch is a Mona-fucking-Lisa.
好了 闭嘴吧 里斯 游戏开始
Okay, hey, shut the fuck up, Reece. Guys, it is game time.
游戏的名字是 点赞或拍砖推文
The game is Good Tweet, Bad Tweet!
哇靠
Oh, shit!
好的 你们这群疯子
Okay. You crazy fuckers
最好在被叫到之前就做好准备
better have these ready when I call them out.
-开始吧  -好的... 点赞推文
- Start it already. - Okay. And... good tweet!
"好的 盟友不总是以我们喜欢的方式出现
"Okay. Allies, don't always come in the form we like.
但肯德尔·罗伊的行为很重要且勇敢"
But what Kendall Roy did was important and brave."
哇哦 就是这样
Boom! Boom, that's the shit!
好了 好了 拍砖推文
All right, all right, all right. Bad tweet.
我来说 我来
I got it, I got it, I got it.
-拍砖 拍砖  -"肯德尔·罗伊才不是什么英雄 哥们
- Bad tweet. Bad tweet. - "Kendall Roy is not a hero, fam.
他是有恋父情结的盗版罗斯"
He's bootleg Ross with a daddy complex."
-爱死这个了 爱死了  -好了 好了
- Love it! Love it! - Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
-该念点赞推文了  -继续继续 不要停 友友们
- Good tweet, good tweet. - Okay. Keep them coming, motherfuckers.
"或许只是因为他指责他的混蛋老爹
"Maybe it's just because he's murking his shitty dad,
但我竟然有点想睡肯德尔·罗伊"
But I kind of wanna fuck Kendall Roy?"
-哇哦 天啊  -可以啊 妹子
- Oh, hell yeah! Booyah! - Yeah, girl.
-拍砖 拍砖  -来啊 来啊
- Bad tweet, bad tweet, bad tweet. - Hit me up. Hit me up.
拍砖 拍砖 拍砖
Bad tweet, bad tweet, bad tweet, bad tweet, bad tweet.
听这个 "他显然有心理疾病和强烈的负罪感
Okay. "He clearly has mental health issues and crazy guilt
还有毒瘾 就是这样 悲哀至极"
Coupled with addiction. That's all this is and it's sad."
烂透了 烂透了
That one sucked! That one sucked!
-你好啊  -你好
- Hi! - Hi!
-你好  -我们快点
- Hi! Wow. - Let's speed it up, fellas.
-我该做点什么吗  -可以啊
- Should I give them something? - Yeah.
打倒父权主义
Fuck the patriarchy!
好了 我们有逃离这里的安全词吗
All right. Do we have like a safe word to get out of here?
失陪
Excuse me.
了不起的西沃恩·罗伊 很高兴见到你
Shiv-fucking-Roy. Great to see you here.
我每次都来
I always come.
光临新闻工作者保障和福利委员会吗
The Committee for the Protection and Welfare of Journalists?
你支持这个委员会 是因为你喜欢把他们关在笼子里吧
You're into that, but you like to keep them protected in hutches, correct?
用那种小奶瓶 就像是喂仓鼠那样的 对吗
With the little feeding bottles, kind of like hamsters?
对 多可爱 我们确实养活了很多报社
Yeah. Yeah. Adorable. We do keep more newspapers alive
而且是全世界雇佣记者最多的企业
and employ more journalists worldwide
所以大概是尽了自己的一份力吧
than any other company, so I guess we're doing our bit?
苏联也雇佣了不少记者啊
The Soviet Union employed a ton of journalists, too.
纳特 这么快就说到斯大林了吗
Oh, Nate, we got to Stalin so fast?
吉尔还会不小心出现在"今日俄罗斯"上吗
Is Gil still turning up on Russia Today by mistake?
-你好啊 哥们  -你好 肯
- Hey. Hey, man. - Hey, Ken.
-很高兴见到你  -原来是家务事
- Good to see you. - It's a family affair.
对 我没想到你会来
Yeah, I didn't think you'd be here. I thought
我以为韦斯达·罗伊科的新任总裁会忙不过来呢
the newly-minted President of Waystar Royco would just be too busy.
-我是顾问  -对哦
- I'm on the advisory. - Oh, right.
你才是动物园里的新头牌
You're the newest attraction at the zoo,
半人半诺贝尔奖吗
half man, half Nobel Prize?
当然 小西 你说中了
Oh, sure, Shiv. You got me.
好吧 小西 很高兴遇到你 真的
Well, well, well, Shiv. Really nice to see you, really.
他怎么样 像州博览会上愤怒的猪吗
So how is he? Is he, like, angry hog at the state fair,
在粪便里打滚 打骂孩子吗
rolling in shit, snapping at kids?
他很好 他在担心你会进公司
He's fine. He's worried you might come in.
让他担心吧
Let him worry.
那很愚蠢 肯
Okay. Well, that would just be dumb, Ken.
我们都需要赢得股东投票
We all need for us to win the shareholder vote.
你也是 所以就再等一周
You, too. So just, you know, just wait a week.
或者少接点采访吧 在这个节骨眼上
And maybe cool it on the interviews while you're at it?
-那会是明智之举  -是的 可能吧
- That'd be smart all round. - Oh. Well, yeah. Maybe.
我不是自杀式炸弹袭击者 小西
I'm not a suicide bomber, Shiv.
我想说的是 在拉瓦家
Hey, I wanted to say, um, just at Rava's?
我应该是对的 我是对的
I think I'm right, I am right,
我可能话说得比较难听
but I maybe threw a couple of ugly rocks.
但我现在在努力变得成熟
I'm just trying to be more thoughtful now.
所以...
So...
我...
Look, I...
我想我们其实目标一致
I think we have the same aim here is the truth.
大局来看 我他妈也烦透了那些糟心事
You know, big picture. I am fucking tired of all this shit, too.
我在尽力推动改革
And I'm pushing for change.
难道你就不能停止口出狂言 无差别打击
Like, is there a world where you stop being gross and throwing stones
我们互相认同然后携手重建
and we can acknowledge and rebuild,
最后达成和解
you know, truth and reconciliation.
或许 我们可以想办法从内部解决问题
You know, and maybe we can actually find a way to fucking fix things
毕竟这样问题才都能迎刃而解
from the inside, which is the only place that anything ever gets done anyway.
他们让你盛装出席就为说这些
They made you get all dressed up for this?
还是说你压根不在乎
Or do you not actually give a fuck?
纯粹就为了自我满足
And it's all just ego?
看啊
Look at this.
现在是你了
It's you now.
"女士们先生们 有请我们的..."
"Ladies and gentlemen, to present our..."
真为你难过 西沃恩
I'm sorry for you, Siobhan.
"比起成为新闻焦点
"Who is used to owning the
更习惯掌控新闻的男人 肯德尔·罗伊"
news rather than being in the news, Kendall Roy."
新闻工作者保障和福利委员会
感谢您抽出时间
So thanks for making time and,
新闻工作者保障和福利委员会
我们要讨论的第一部分是
when we do it, the first section will just be
-南亚流媒体事宜  -对
- the South Asian streaming stuff? - Yeah.
我们还会问股东大会的问题
We'll have to ask the shareholder meeting question.
-我非常自信 百分百乐观  -很好
- I'm very confident. Massive optimism. - Great.
然后 你也知道我们有打算
And then, you know, I think that you know that there's this idea
在聊完之后开放聊一些家庭八卦
that everyone felt it'd be really kind of fun if after everything we might,
会让所有人觉得很有意思
open up the door on some family stuff for a little bit.
我懂 我懂 我们不会大做文章
No, I know, I know. And we won't dwell on it, so,
就轻松聊聊 随心所欲一点 怎么样
we'll just keep it loose and, it'd be fun to freewheel it, hmm?
把他们准备的问题一字不差地告诉我
Tell me precisely every single word they're gonna ask me.
根据泛美网科商业制度
Well, I couldn't disclose specific questions
我不能透露具体的问题
because of our policies at ATN Business
这有违职业道德 你也知道
and that would be ethically, you know.
不过 大概会是这样
But, it's, it might be something like
"洛根看起来是个工作狂
"Logan seems like a business- oriented guy,
有没有什么特别的事情是你和你爸很喜欢一起做的呢
What's something special " that you and your dad enjoy doing together?"
-没有 下一个  -好的
- No! Next question. - Okay. Sure.
"说说在你需要帮助的时候
"What was a time that your dad
你爸为你挺身而出的例子"
came to your aid when you really needed him?"
-别 不要这个问题  -好
- No. We're not doing that one. - Right.
"你最珍贵的父子回忆是什么"
"What is your most cherished father-son memory?"
这些问题都不行
So far, these are bad.
那 那你来提起话头怎么样
Well, how about, how about you lead?
你有没有什么想讲的童年温情小故事
Is there some sort of childhood, uh, story that you'd like to tell?
我对老宅子有点回忆
I got a memory in the old bankiola.
在蒙大拿州钓鱼的往事
Some fly-fishing in Montana,
-不错  -如果你们感兴趣的话
- Sure. - If that interests you.
非常感谢 罗伊先生
Thank you, Mr. Roy!
好的 我会转达的
Um, well, I will pass that along.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
我不想让他...
And I don't want him...
-你还好吗  -被爱情和婚姻"滋润"着
- How are you doing? - Love and marriage.
我感觉她们每啧一声 我就又有一百万打水漂了
I feel another million drain with every cluck from that hen house.
-你见到他了吗  -见到了
- Did you see him? - I did.
-他会进公司吗  -我不知道
- Is he coming in? - I don't know.
我感觉不会 他明白我们的意思了
I don't think so. I think he gets it.
谢谢
Thank you.
每次我看到你不在外边替我说话
You know, every time I don't see you out there saying something,
我就会想 "小西真的爱我吗"
I think, "Does Shiv even like me?"
别这样 罗曼...
Oh, come on. Roman is...
女儿 我唯一的女儿
My daughter. My only daughter.
你到底想让我怎么做
What is it exactly that you want me to do?
我不知道 画个圈困住他吧或许
I don't know. Draw a circle around him, maybe?
公开声明你老爸不是什么卑劣混蛋
Declare that your old man isn't some dirty bastard.
或者说出真相 有关肯德尔的
Tell the truth, maybe, about him.
好啊 真相 公之于众不太好吧
Yeah. The truth, but horrible in public, right?
你信任我吗
Do you trust me?
当然了
Yes, of course.
关于什么
On what?
关于那些风言风语
On all this hullabaloo.
"风言风语"
"Hullabaloo"?
当然
Yeah.
我不...
I don't...
当然
Yeah.
我们能 聊一聊吗
Can we I mean, can we talk?
当然 聊一聊
Yes. We can talk.
好的 我们是个大公司 但...
Okay. Well, we're a big company, but...
到底... 有多糟糕...
how bad is... is...
-那些文件里最糟糕的部分是什么  -没那么坏
What is the worst thing that could be in those papers? - Not all that bad.
我是说 公司经营稳健合规
I mean Um, health, safety, compliance.
只是有几颗老鼠屎
A few bad apples.
-怎么  -我知道这不是实话
- What? - Well, I know that isn't true.
爸 汤姆之前就在邮轮部门工作 比尔什么都说了
Come on, Dad. Tom worked in cruises, Bill told him everything.
而且 我还知道有一些秘密操作
And besides, I know that there were black ops
我知道公司针对受害者和吹哨人进行了恐吓
and I know that there was targeted intimidation of victims and whistleblowers.
那个无真人涉案 我的天
NRPI, for fuck's sake.
确实采取了一些非常措施
Maybe there were some salty moves.
-你不能这么编故事  -我要保证你清白
- You can't just change your story. - I wanna keep you clean.
我让格丽接任 但是我没法相信她
I put Gerri in, but I can't trust her,
她是障眼法 我需要你
she's optics. I need you.
听着 我对这些破事一无所知
Listen, I didn't know about any of this shit.
可是 你是邮件收信人啊
Well, you're on emails.
你知道我一天要收多少封邮件吗
Do you know how many emails I get a day?
我不读邮件 我只看行动方案
I don't read my emails. I get the action points.
-我知道  -小西 这个世界太他妈残酷了
- I know. - Shiv, the world is fucking rough.
我们运行着一条邮轮线
We ran a cruise line out of some
从穷得叮当响的小港口出发 注册在一些鸟不拉屎的地方
tin pot ports registered in bongo fucking bongo hovels
我们投入了上百万的资金
and we poured millions in it, sure.
我们有粗暴对待那些傻逼工会头子
Did we play rough with the odd fucking union boss
或是那些不停上诉的爱发牢骚的怨妇吗
or some Moaning Minnie repeat litigant?
我不知道 这都是二十五年前的事了
I don't know! It was a quarter of a century ago.
大部分都是 所以
A lot of it. So yes.
我 为了你和你的兄弟而战
I fought, for you and your brothers.
但是你不会发现任何一份文件
But you will not find a piece
会让你以我为耻 明白吗
of paper that makes you ashamed of me. Okay?
好吧 但政府确实握有
Well, the government does have an
一手遮天的巨大筹码 爸爸
unbelievable amount of leverage at its disposal, Dad.
-法律  -没错 法律
- The law. - Yeah, the law.
法律代表民心
The law is people.
民心就是政治
And people is politics.
而我可以操控民心
And I can handle the people.
-这表真棒  -它太漂亮了
- Oh, that is nice. - It's just beautiful,
-我是说 它很...  -很重
- I mean, it's just... it's... - It's heavy.
是吧 我会一直很在意我的手腕
Is it? I've always been self-conscious about my wrists,
-这是藏红花  -它可以解决
- It's saffron. - so it could address that.
你的手腕很正常
You have normal wrists.
谢谢 你这么说我很开心
Thanks, that is very nice of you to say.
你的手腕也很漂亮
That is, you have some nice wrists yourself.
格雷格 我们要不要现在把账结了
Greg, do you think we could figure this out?
你准备好转账了吗 四万
You wanna transfer now? It's 40K.
你搞错了 这应该是给我的礼物
Oh, no, no. Um, I think this is, uh, like a gift situation.
肯 肯
Hey, Ken? Hey, Ken?
-你要买吗  -什么
- Are you buying this? - What?
-你要给他买这个吗  -什么 那块表吗
- Are you buying him this? - What? The... the watch?
不 我只说了帮你搞到 兄弟
No. No. I just said I'd hook you up, dude.
你这表情什么意思 别跟我耍性子
What is that look? Don't get weird on me.
我他妈可不是你的金主爸爸 守财奴
I'm not your fucking sugar daddy. Cheapskate.
不是 没… 没关系
No, that's... that's all good, I mean,
-这表值4万美元…  -我才不会买那块破表
- it's $40,000 worth... - I'm not buying that fucking watch.
他在做什么春秋大梦呢
What the fuck is he talking about?
我不能买 我得把它还回去
No, I can't. I'm gonna need to give it back.
现在不合适
It's not a good time.
不行 它已经在你手上轻微包浆了
No, no, no, no, no. It has your patina now.
-没有啊 我没怎么玩  -你答应了的
- No, I don't have patina. - You agreed.
-没有 我洗过澡的  -该死 她... 今晚又发我的视频了
- No, I shower. - Shit, she... did me again tonight.
康福莉 索菲·伊沃比又做了关于我的视频
Hey, hey, Comfry? Sophie Iwobi did me again tonight.
我买 我买还不行么
I'm gonna do it. I'mma do it. Yeah.
-什么  -她做了一段视频
- What? - She did a segment.
-该死  -我们明天再商量对策吧
- Oh, shit. - Should we do this tomorrow, maybe?
-"俄狄孬种"2  -我可以... 可以帮你提炼几个要点
- "Oedipussy 2." - I could... I can get you some bullet points?
看来她要把我撕碎了 来吧 来看看
It looks like she tore me one. Come on, fuck that.
我们得... 我们得看看这个
We gotta... We gotta watch this!
各位 各位 我要播放索菲·伊沃比的视频了
Hey, guys! Guys! I'm gonna put on Sophie Iwobi.
看来她要把我撕碎了
It looks like she tore me one.
来吧 看看这个
Hey, hey. Come on. We should watch this,
很有趣的 开始了
it'll be fun. Here it is.
索菲评混乱
让我们来关注一下
So let's turn for a moment
肯德尔·罗伊 我最喜欢的白人男性
to Kendall Roy Whoo-hoo! My favorite white man.
俄狄孬种 第二章
富豪告密者 或者如你所知
Snitchy Rich. Or as you may know him
-"穿普拉达的蛋黄酱"  -好的吧
- "A jar of mayonnaise in a Prada suit." - Ha! Okay.
罗伊今天早些时候发推 "我们必须颠覆这种"
"Roy tweeted earlier today, "We must overthrow the culture"
没关系 想笑就笑
It's okay, you can laugh.
"让女性沉默的腐朽文化"
"Of corruption that silences women."
-他到底在说什么鬼话  -阿门
- The fuck is he talking about? - Amen.
这好比你的狗说
That's like your dog saying,
"各位 我们要惩罚那些
"Hey, guys, guys, we have to punish
乱翻垃圾桶吃咖啡渣
Whoever ate coffee grounds out of the trash
然后在沙发上拉屎的玩意儿"
and then shit on the sofa."
帖子主题 沙发正义
Hashtag Sofa Justice.
-真厉害  -真正的进步派人士一直在拥护
- That's great. - Actual progressives have been embracing
这个家伙 为什么
This dude. Why?
这家伙在一个月前告诉国会
This is the guy who told Congress like a month ago
自己父亲所受的调查是一场政治迫害
that the investigation into his father was a witch hunt.
同时他也是这张照片中的那个卢瑟
And he's also the fail-bro who once posed in this photo
-该死  -曾经在让·乔治餐厅外
- Oh, shit. - "Flashing gang signs"
-展示帮派手势  -好了 她太夸张了
- Outside of Jean Georges. - Okay. That is such a reach.
-你只是在开玩笑而已  -她好爱我啊
- You were being tongue-in-cheek. - She fucking loves me.
所以 问题在于 肯德尔·罗伊身患重病
See, the problem is, Kendall Roy suffers from a severe case
这是爱 都是出于爱
This is love, it's all love.
医生称之为"白种人富脑症"
Of what doctors call Caucasian Rich Brain.
事实是 就基因而言
What happens is, genetically
继承的财富和白人血统会导致
inherited wealth and whiteness can cause neural pathways
大脑中的神经通路收缩
In the brain to constrict
让病人以为自己是清醒的
and make the patient believe he's woke
而实际上却是个彻头彻尾的混蛋
When he's just a total fucking jackass.
-他当然错了 谢谢  -我觉得我应该继续下去
- Of course he's done wrong. Thank you. - I feel like I should go on.
你觉得呢 你能再联系一下吗
What do you think? Can you touch base?
我觉得应该先和贝里谈谈
I think we should talk to Berry
因为还有很多方法可以应对民意反弹
because there's a couple ways to counter backlash,
-这可能不是最佳选择  -民意反弹 这是...
- and it might not be the best. - Backlash? This is...
-这不叫...  -这叫身处热点话题
- This is not... - This is being in the conversation.
-是的  -这他妈太棒了
- Yeah - This is fucking great.
-太棒了  -是的
- This is great. - Yeah.
小西西
Shivy!
-你的人怎么样 见到他了吗  -见到了
- How was your guy? Did you see him? - Yup.
是的 我到家的时候
Yeah. When I got in,
蒙代尔吃了你的丝袜
Mondale had eaten some of your pantyhose
我得把它们从他菊花里拉出来
and I had to pull them out of his ass.
我的天啊 对不起
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
你不应该随地乱扔的 西沃恩
You shouldn't leave them lying around on the floor, Siobhan.
-佣人走之后可不行  -好的
- Not once the help have gone. - Yeah.
你没事吧
You okay?
蒙代尔不太好 躁动不安
Mondale's not well. Mondale's unsettled.
肯德尔要进韦斯达吗
Is, Kendall coming in to Waystar?
我觉得不会
I don't think so.
-你的人怎么样了  -我的人怎么样了
- How is your guy? - How is my guy?
是的 我们... 我列举了一个
Yeah. We... I outlined what might have
无名氏部门主管可能会遇到的问题
happened to a theoretical John Doe, divisional head.
然后 我们讨论了一下
And, you know, we talked about
如果调查结果出来
if what comes out does come out
事实真相曝光的话 他说
in terms of the investigation, and he said
"这个无名氏如果最后没有锒铛入狱
"It's very difficult to see a world
基本属于奇迹"
in which this John Doe doesn't go to jail."
-所以  -好吧 该死
- So. - Right. Fuck.
汤姆 没事的
Tom, it'll be okay.
你有什么证据来说服我吗 我很好奇
And what evidence do you have for that? I'm curious.
汤姆 亲爱的
Tom, honey?
我确实有个馊主意
I did have one dumb idea.
我在想 也许…
I was thinking, you know, maybe...
也许提前接受这个结果会比较好
maybe it would be good to get out in front of it.
如果免不了牢狱之灾 或许我能从中捞到点好处
If prison is likely, could I find any benefit in that, you know?
-你是说合作吗  -不 不是和司法部合作
- You mean cooperate? - No, not with DOJ.
是和你爸
Your dad.
我去找你爸 然后… 自告奋勇当替罪羊
I go to your dad and I... I offer myself up as the beating post.
不行 亲爱的 你不能去
Uh, no, honey, you can't.
不行 亲爱的 你喝多了
No. Honey, you're drunk.
但确实很明智
But it is smart.
是的 这有点像… 绝地逢生
Yeah. It's, kind of a... A win from a no-win.
-你真这样想吗  -是啊 简单粗暴
- You think? - Yeah. I mean, it's punchy.
我是说 很可能最终没人会去坐牢
I mean, you know, it's very likely that no one goes to prison.
-是的  -无论如何 你都给我爸留下了好印象
- Yeah. - And either way, you bank gold with my dad.
这个提议很高明
The offer is kind of genius.
不出意外 一切顺利的话
All being well, you know, with a fair wind,
不到一年我就能出狱了
I could be done in less than a year.
但是不行 你不能去 汤姆
But, no, you can't, Tom.
天啊 现在所有人都他妈要为他赴汤蹈火
Jesus. Everyone's doing fucking somersaults for him right now.
这家伙在一个月前告诉国会
And he told congress like a month ago
自己父亲所受的调查是一场政治迫害
That the investigation into his father was a witch hunt.
同时他也是这张照片中的卢瑟
And he's also the fail-bro who once posed in this photo,
曾经在让·乔治餐厅外展示帮派标语
flashing gang signs Outside of Jean-Georges.
可怜的小肯
Poor Kenny
问题是 肯德尔·罗伊身患重病
See, the problem is Kendall Roy suffers from a severe case
米歇尔·安·范德霍文 白宫高级助理
医生称之为"白种人富脑症"
"Of what doctors call Caucasian Rich Brain."
米歇尔·安·范德霍文 白宫高级助理
杰西
Hey, Jess.
-我要进公司  -"好 进办公室吗"
- I'm going in. - "Oh, okay. To the office?"
-是的  -什么时候
- Okay. Yeah. - When?
-现在  -但你说...
- Now. - But you said...
是的 我说过这个想法很错误
Yeah. I said that was a false thought.
把我的办公室准备好
Just make sure my office is ready.
我到之前发短信给你
I'll ping you before I arrive.
没问题吧 很好
Good? Good? Great.
格雷格 我要进公司了
Greg. Yo. Hey, I'm going in.
是的 我可能要大干一场
Yeah. I might wanna roll deep,
所以... 别走漏风声 知道吗
so, uh, just keep it on the down-low, okay?
我想看看能激起多大震荡
I wanna see the shockwaves.
-十一月即将来临  -你好
- November just around the corner - Hi.
非常重要的选举…
Very important election..
应该快结束了
Shouldn't be too long now.
从某种意义上说 他已经
Well, he has already brought more voters,
赢得了更多的选民 通过增加…
in a sense, by increasing...
是的 我一直 一直…
Yeah, because I've, you know, I've been, I've been...
我一直在想
I've been thinking, um,
你现在真正需要的是什么
about what it is that you might really need right now,
还有我能提供什么帮助
and,  and how I can help.
对 因为
Yeah. Yeah. Because, you know,
假如说事情真的按所想的那样发展
if, if things go how they could go,
或许不会有什么负面影响 但如果没有
maybe there's no repercussions. But if not,
那就有可能会损失资产
there'll probably be a cash number
而且很有可能会需要
and there will probably
一两个人关到铁窗里面 对吧
need to be a face or two behind bars, right?
你到底想说什么 汤姆
What's your angle, Tom?
没什么 只是
No, none. None. Just just
我可能就在攻击范围内
I'm probably in the firing line.
而我只是想说
And I just wanted you to know
如果战略上有需要 我可以背这个锅
if you need to strategize, I can be that guy.
我会为你赴汤蹈火
I'll step up and go down.
就这些吗
That's it?
你就没什么想要的吗
You don't want anything?
没有 没有 我就想说这些
No. No. It's just there.
只要你需要我 我绝不会犹豫[扭动]
If you need it. I won't wriggle.
尽管对着鳟鱼的头敲吧 我会乖乖躺进你的包里
Just clonk the trout on the head and put it in your pouch.
不会走到那一步的
It won't come to that.
不过...
But...
还是谢谢你 汤姆 谢谢
thank you, Tom. Thank you.
-没事 -他所做的一切 有助于我们
- Not a problem. - All he's doing, helping us to get
把观点传达给了那些已经改变想法
our message out to Latino voters who've really come around
与总统先生的观点一致的拉丁裔选民
to the President's message and, you know,
我们也看到几天前鲍耶上了你的节目
we saw Boyer on your program a few nights ago.
-没错  -没错 这也回应了总统 所以说...
- Absolutely. - Absolutely. Much for the president so...
这里是伯格曼 亨顿与韦斯律师事务所
Bergman, Hendon, and Weiss.
你好 你好
Hello. Hi.
我是从一个朋友那得知
I was given your number
你们这的号码的 我想
by a friend of mine and I was wanting to
我想和雷克斯·亨顿先生约时间见个面
I would like to schedule an appointment with Rex Hendon?
-请问是咨询吗  -没错
- This is for a consultation? - That's right.
不好意思 你能稍等一下吗
Excuse me, can you hold the line one second?
-格雷格 什么事 快点说 我很忙  -是这样的
- Greg, talk fast. What is it? I'm busy. - Hey, so...
有件事你们可能会想知道
So I have something that you guys might wanna know.
-谢谢  -这个给您
- Thank you. - Here you go.
最近怎么样啊
Hey! How you doing?
非常好 你是... 你到这有何贵干
Great. Are you... what are you doing down here?
马克 这小子的表现可真不赖
Mark, isn't he the just fucking greatest?
-当然 没错  -一如既往 你能发言真是太好了
- Sure. Yeah. - As ever, great to have you contribute.
能占用你五分钟谈谈吗
Could we do five on what we need to do here?
当然
Sure.
事情怎么样了
So how are things?
瞧瞧你 还是这么坚挺
Look at you, the tough guy!
你连法院的传票都不接受 对吧
You wouldn't even take service of a subpoena, right?
那可不 我儿子现在翅膀硬了 在外面兴风作浪
Yeah. My son stands up, waves his dick in the air,
整个世界现在都得依着他的想法来吗
and the rest of the world is meant to re-arrange itself according to his liking?
-我可不这么想 你说是吧  -我明白了
- I don't think so, right? - I see.
既然你都布置好一切了 那你会好好配合他们吗
But are you gonna get more cooperative now that you've set the table?
这简直就是迫害
It's a witch hunt.
那些检察官会后悔他们在这里
The prosecutors are gonna
所投入的一切人力物力的
regret any time or money they spend on it.
-老头怎么看  -他倒没什么想法
- What does the old man think? - Not fucking much.
可不 他现在得整日整夜为那些
No, he's got he's got poll numbers
变来变去的民调数字操心呢
dancing in front of his eyes morning, noon, and night.
如果有人在威斯康星州惹了乱子
So someone shits in Wisconsin,
他就担心密西西比州会受此影响
he's worried it'll float down
搞不好连爱荷华州的支持率也会下降
the Mississippi and hurt his numbers in Iowa.
放心 有我们在呢
Relax. We've got his back!
那就好 这很好
Yeah, well that's great.
我觉得 你也知道的 一开始
I guess, you know, when this thing
出乱子的时候 大家都以为"洛根·罗伊快要不行了"
broke the whole thing was, "Logan Roy's going down."
但到了现在 人们又开始
But then you got this thing, some of
在那说 "罗伊绝不可能倒的"
our folks are like, "There's no way Roy's going down."
"总统会在背后护着他 这个体制已经烂了"
"The President's gonna protect him. The system is broken!"
人们摸不着头脑
People have no idea.
都是一群得了妄想症的人
They have these paranoid fantasies.
说得没错
Yeah.
我不需要你为我做任何事
I don't want you to do anything.
没错
Right.
我什么都不需要
What I want is, is nothing.
顾虑不应该在这些废话上
Normal consideration not to become the focus of some bullshit.
-没错  -绝对不行
- Right. - Not favors.
-没错  -没错 没错 没错
- Right. - Right, right, right, right, right.
-怎么了  -事实是
- What? - The fact is,
我不需要任何人为我做任何事
I don't want anything from anyone.
这一向不是我的行事之道 但我倒是很希望
That's not the way I operate, but I would like to know
假如我坚持到最后 可不要有人临阵脱逃
that no one's gonna shit their pants if I hang tough.
脸书上全是你和领导 在保守党会议和达沃斯论坛上的照片
Facebook is full of photos of you and the boss at CPAC and Davos.
你们还为彼此说了那么多好话
All the nice things you've said about each other?
这都对我们重点专注的选民产生了不良影响
It hits the demographic we have to worry about.
如果老家伙对我见死不救
If that Raisin hangs me out to dry,
我很乐意对他加倍奉还
I'm quite willing to do the same to him.
既然我们打开天窗说亮话了
Well, if we're gonna be real,
或许总统觉得你最近的报道
maybe the president has not been feeling
既没什么作用 也不是很真实
like your coverage has been very helpful or truthful lately.
我他妈还可以搞得他更难堪
It could get a lot fucking worse!
我们的利益是一致的
We have the same interest here.
你能降一降舆论热度吗 之后我再看看怎么帮上忙
Can you lower the temperature? And I'll see what I can do.
当然 正有此意
Sure. That's all I need.
-失陪  -我们让每一个人通过内部网络
- Excuse me. - So we asked everyone to submit
匿名提交他们目前的疑虑和困惑
concerns and questions anonymously via the Intranet.
但这也存在着不足 正如你所见
Which has some drawbacks, as you know,
还有我们必须得提醒你 小西
and we wanted you to be aware, Shiv.
等到你上台的时候
If you're gonna be up there,
我们打算把这些投到一个屏幕上
so we plan to put these on, a screen
-他们都问了什么问题  -大意差不多是
- And what are they asking? - Well, the general tenor is,
"到底出了什么事啊"
"What the hell's happening here?"
很多这样的问题
A lot of those.
还有这种 "我没有脸告诉我妈
also, "I'm embarrassed to say
我在韦斯达公司工作 有什么建议吗"
to my mother I work at Waystar. Any advice?"
-有啊 让你妈去死  -"哪怕只是冰山一角"
- Yeah, fuck your mother. - "Please tell us anything at all"
-"也请告诉我们到底怎么了"  -我的天哪
- "About what is happening here." - Oh, God.
他们是用蜡笔写的这些问题吗
Did they write these questions in crayon?
我的讲稿已经准备好了
I mean, I have my speech all set.
真的还有必要回答这些问题吗
Do we even really need to have questions?
我们之前的确说过希望解答一些疑问 所以说...
Well, we did say we wanted to answer questions, so...
-没错 所以他们安排了  -那好吧 爸可见不得这个问题
- Yeah. There we go. - Okay. Well, dad can't see this one
-这个也不行  -这个更不行
- or this one. - Oh, fuck no.
-会把他气到拉裤子  -不行 不行
- This will make him shit his Pop Tarts. - No, no.
-我觉得这里面只有三个能用的  -好的
- I think there's like three here we can use. - Okay.
-三个就够了 -这个也太他妈粗鲁了
- Three is all we need. - But this is just fucking rude.
-这个甚至都不能算是一个问题  -好的
- I mean, it's not even really a question. - Okay.
我觉得人们根本不能对这个环节抱有什么幻想
I mean, I don't think people should even be thinking this that work here.
-没错  -还有其他稍微不一样的问题吗 比如
- You're right. - Can we get different questions like
-少些质疑性的问题  -对
- less question-y questions? - Yeah.
-因为这些问题实在是太恐怖了  -当然有
- 'Cause these are just fucking horrible. - We can.
-好吧 我和雨果也准备了一系列问题  -来点别的
- Okay. Well, Hugo and I did prepare a set of questions - Something else.
问的都是大家真正想知道的内容
that are of the sort of things that people would actually wanna know.
-很好  -没错 我们认为这些
- Great. - Yeah. I mean these, we feel,
-才是大家真正想问的问题  -我们有麻烦了
- are people's real questions, okay? - We've got a problem.
-洛根让你们去趟他的办公室  -现在吗
- Logan wants to see you in his office. - Now?
-您好  -是丽莎
- Hello? - Lisa.
好丽莎 咱们的律界精英
Lisa! The Regal Legal Eagle.
肯德尔 我听说你要进公司
Kendall, I hear you're going in.
你搞哪样啊
"What the fuck?"
没错 我可不能让他主宰战场走向 丽莎
Yeah. I can't let him dominate the battlespace, Lisa.
我妹妹已经在行动了 我不能坐视不管
My sister is making moves, I can't just watch it happen.
关于免责协议想出什么招了吗
What... what's the story on my immunity?
[检察官和嫌犯的协定 罪犯提供关键的犯罪信息以换取宽大处理]
肯德尔 我觉得就走"一日女王"的形式吧
"I'm figuring out a "Queen for a Day" Situation, Kendall."
-在这儿 我要能说了算  -对 但是我们快没有气势了
- "I have to have control here." - Yeah, but we're losing the momentum.
我们能搞个突袭吗 突袭怎么样 我们能搞一个吗
Can we get a raid? What about a raid? Can we get a raid?
我们什么都"搞"不到
"We can't "Get" Anything."
好吧 但真的不行吗
No, sure. But really?
我们已经打动他们了
I mean, we hit the right buttons.
难道政府面对大企业就要放松监管吗
Has the government gone soft-cock on Big Corp?
丽莎 我四十分钟后打给你 你说了算 再见
I'll call you in 40, Lisa. You're the boss here! Bye.
我们和伊沃比合作吧 好吗 就这么做 联系她
And let's commit to Iwobi. Yeah? Let's do it. Reach out.
[美国脱口秀演员, 主持著名政治吐槽节目"每日秀"]
联系崔娃 给我写点段子
Call Noah and get me some jokes.
要超越段子 神搞笑的那种
Not jokes, like, funny as fuck shit,
而不是傻乎乎的那种
but not in a stupid jokey way.
真的吗 他在来的路上了吗
Is it true? He's on his way?
卑鄙小人
Fucking rat.
我要把万宝龙[手表]塞到他的喉咙里
I'm gonna jam a Montblanc down his fucking throat.
-爸 他想要的就是闹剧  -凯莉
- He'll eat up any drama, Dad. - Kerry!
我们不如就放他进来 把他当做透明人
Look, why don't we just let him come on in and ignore him?
把科林找来 还有大楼的后勤服务
Get us Colin, get us building services.
如果他冲我来 我要把他卡住
If he comes for me, I want him fucking cuffed.
-好的  -他被炒了
- Okay. - He's fired!
人力资源部正在讨论他卸任的事宜 如果开除他
HR is discussing him stepping down from his duties, but firing?
你就相当于亲手给司法部递了个汽油桶
You would be handing DOJ a gas can.
-我同意  -这会是一场公关灾难
- Yeah. - It would be a PR disaster.
需要我联系外部法律顾问吗
Want me to get outside counsel on the line?
前台说他在停车了
Front desk says he's pulling up.
我不希望任何人看见他 给我拦住他
I don't want people seeing him. Keep him the fuck out!
你好吗
How are you?
先生 抱... 抱歉
Sir. I'm... I'm sorry.
-什么  -你的门禁卡已经失效了
- Yeah? - Your keycard has expired.
-失效了吗 真奇怪  -肯德尔
- Expired? That's weird. - Hi, Kendall.
-真是个疯狂的早上  -是吗
- Uh, bit of a crazy morning here. - Oh, is it?
你愿意的话 我们可以去北边43号[餐馆] 我给你汇报下情况
If you like, we could head over to 43 North and I can fill you in.
在那儿会比较舒服
Might be a little bit more comfortable there.
我不要去卫星办公室 谢谢
Yeah. Not going to the satellite office. Thanks.
我的卡刷不了 所以
My card doesn't work, so I'm
我打算翻过门禁 让雷米拍下来
just gonna hurdle the gates and have Remi film it.
什么 不 谁是... 我们一起上楼怎么样
What? No, who's... How about we go up with you?
我们一起上楼 我们会把你刷进来的
We go up together. We'll swipe you in.
你们想一起进来吗
You guys wanna sync up?
-他们不能上去  -因为他们... 他们邀请我去...
- They can't go up. - 'Cause they... They're inviting me to...
-不 他可以上去  -他不能上去
- No. He can go up. - He can't go up.
他们告诉我们不能放他上去
They told us he can't go up.
真的吗 不好意思 请问"他们"是谁
Really? Sorry, who's "They"?
-"他们"是谁  -我们不能批准你进去
- Who's "They"? - We can't authorize that.
-就是...  -我可以批准他进来
- Well... - I can authorize that.
-我现在就在批准他进来  -让...
- I am authorizing that. - Let... Hey...
我们没准阻止不了他在员工大会上捣乱 对吗
We probably can't keep him out of the town hall, correct?
考虑到他的处境 你可以阻拦他参与
"You can discourage him from attending in light of his position."
我们可以用电击枪阻拦他吗
Can we discourage him with a taser
直接打在他的鸡鸡或蛋蛋
shot directly to his peni or scrummage sacking?
-他往货梯走了  -行吧
- He's headed for the freight. - Fine.
用升降架把他像个汉堡包一样运上来
Bring him up in the dumbwaiter like a fucking hamburger.
-最近怎么样 兄弟  -你好
- All right. What's up, bro? - Hey.
-在搬重物吗  -对的
- Doing the heavy lifting. - Yeah.
他到了吗
Is he there?
我还没看到他愚蠢地走来
I don't see him yet with his stupid walk.
汤姆 把信科部门的山姆和雷找来
Tom, get Sam and Ray in IT,
确保他没跟信科部门的人套近乎
and make sure he doesn't get fucking cute with IT.
兄弟
Hey, man.
-兄弟 见到你真好  -你好
- Good to see you, man. Hey, man. - Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
-你好  -有点奇怪 对吧
- Hey. - Kind of weird, right?
-相当奇怪  -对的
- It's pretty weird. - Yeah.
-但是... 你懂的  -最近怎么样
- But, you know, yeah. - How's it going?
生活总要继续
Yeah. Life goes on, you know? Yeah.
佛系啊 不错 生活总要继续
Buddhist. Nice. Life does go on.
所以我爸的办公室里在搞些什么鬼
So what so what's going on back there in my dad's office?
他和白宫的联系人有什么秘密沟通渠道吗
He got any backchannel White House contacts in there or what?
-我开玩笑的 你也不会跟我说  -对啊
- I'm joking. You can't tell me that. - Right. Right, right.
你和司法部达成了免责协议吗
And do you have an immunity deal with DOJ?
-你们达成协议了吗  -真好 我们可以这样开玩笑
- Do you? - It's good we can kid around like this.
但是 兄弟 其实你在一个很艰难的位置
But look, man, you're actually in a difficult spot.
我知道 当... 当紫禁城里的最后一个太监很煎熬
I know it's... it's no fun being the last fucking eunuch in the forbidden city.
我很好
I'm doing fine.
汤姆 我喜欢你 我和你之间没有恩怨过往
Well, I like you and I have no beef with you, Tom.
兄弟 新生活是有无限可能的
Another life is possible, brother.
他不是在亲汤姆 就是在拉拢他
He's trying to kiss or nibble Tom.
别让这件事变成了诺曼底登陆战 好吗
Let's just not turn this into the Invasion of Normandy, okay?
-2010...  -行吧
- 2010.... - Okay. Okay.
肯德尔·罗伊
账户被锁了
Locked out.
肯德尔·罗伊
你们感觉冷吗
Does it feel cold to you in here?
-是吧  -是... 是吗
- Right? - It... Is it?
开什么玩笑
You got to be kidding me.
对 他们... 他们黑了我的空调
Yeah, yeah. They've... they've... they've hacked my AC.
我觉得... 我觉得是68华氏度[20摄氏度] 正是你想要的
I think... I think this is a 68, how you like it.
68 这他妈不可能有68华氏度
68? This isn't 68, no fucking way.
感觉只有65 62华氏度 当然会觉得冷
This is like 65, 62. Definitely feels a little cool.
-雷米  -怎么了
- Okay, Remi. - Yeah.
-我隔空投送个购物清单给你  -好的
-I'm airdropping you a little shopping list. - Okay.
-你能很快搞定吗  -我可以
- You gonna come back stat? - I can do that.
员工大会什么时候开始
What time does the town hall start?
两点
Um, two o'clock.
-两点吗 好的  -对
- Two o'clock? Okay. - Yeah.
有事吗
Yeah.
怎么了
What?
来看看情况
Just checking in.
好吧 我只是在...
Okay. Yeah. I'm just...
我知道你
I know you.
所以 你准备好了吗
So, if you're ready?
我爸会到场吗
Will my dad be there?
削弱我的权威
Undermining my authority?
他会在附近 强化你的权威
He'll be nearby emphasizing your authority.
整栋大楼都会现场直播
The live feed will be streaming through the whole building
还有全球主要的办公室
and to all major offices globally.
你需要任何东西 我都会在
And anything you need, I'll be here.
顺便一提 祝贺你
Congratulations, by the way.
我一直都在为你进入公司努力争取
I was always pushing for you to
以我的方式 我觉得这...
be brought in in my own little way. I think this...
现在让我们欢迎我们的新国内总裁 西沃恩·罗伊
And now please welcome our new Domestic President, Siobhan Roy.
谢谢大家 谢谢 谢谢卡洛丽娜
Thank you all. Thank you. Thank you, Karolina.
我就长话短说了
Okay, so I will keep this straightforward.
韦斯达的一位高管
A senior executive at Waystar
这个人也恰巧是我的哥哥
who also happens to be a senior brother of mine,
我觉得我这样说是合法的
I think I can legally say that,
作出了非常严厉的指控
has made some very serious allegations
而我们对待这些指控也很严肃
and as we take those allegations seriously,
你们未来会理解的
there is, you'll understand,
有很多我们不能公开合法谈论的事情
a fair amount that we can't talk about legally.
但是 在我心里这依然是个家族事业
However, this is still a family operation in spirit
你们都是这个家庭的一员
and you are all a part of that family.
正如我们能够告诉你们的 我们希望告诉你们的
So as much as we can tell you, you know, we want to tell you,
我是西沃恩·罗伊 韦斯达国内运营的新总裁
I'm Siobhan Roy, Waystar's new President of Domestic Operations.
我非常以及极其地关注企业的责任
And I'm paying particular and specific attention to corporate responsibility.
我知道你们中的一些人有担忧
I know that some of you have concerns,
但在这里我想告诉你们 我们懂
and I'm here to tell you we get it.
如果邮轮事件曾经犯下了错误
If mistakes have been made historically at Cruises,
我们会发现问题 并且实施...
we are going to identify them and implement, uh...
而且 个人问责
What's more, personal accountability
是韦斯达四个核心经营理念之一 雨果
is one of the four core pillars of the Waystar philosophy. Hugo?
-我在  -处理一下 谢谢
- Yeah. Yeah. - We got that. Thank you.
有些人或许会认为这个问题是个笑话
Some people might think this, issue is a joke,
但我们向你们保证 我们非常重视这个问题
but we, assure you, we take it very seriously.
谢谢
Just... Thank you.
快去看看到底怎么回事
Go and find what the fuck is going on, please.
我们会确保那些
So we are going to ensure that those who engaged in any actions
不仅是犯了错的在职人员
that went beyond mere mistakes,
更加... 有意义...
to more purpos-ul... Purposeful...
能处理下这个情况吗
Can we get that sorted?
我向你们保证 尽管这里有人捣乱
I assure you, we take this issue very seriously
但我们会严肃地对待这一情况
even if someone here is not.
全他妈的搞砸了
Fucking ruined it.
我很抱歉 小宝
Sorry, Pinky.
现在你看到了吧
Now do you see? Huh?
-肯  -你好
- Hey, Ken. - Hey.
多谢
Thanks.
快好了吗 几点了
Are we close? What time is it?
现在几点了[现在是什么时代]
Oh, what time is it?
就像是在18世纪似的
Oh, it's, it's like the 18th century
手表都停了
or something when watches didn't work.
-手表停了  -是的
- It doesn't work? - No.
那你干嘛买它
Why did you get it?
我干嘛买它 是你怂恿我的
Why did I get it? You encouraged me.
你不记得了吗
You don't remember this?
你对我耸耸肩 就好像买它很合理一样
You shrugged at me like it was reasonable.
-这个不错  -但我没让你买停了的手表啊
- This one's good. - Not if it doesn't work.
行 好吧  我就是个卑微的保管员
It's fine. It's okay. I I'm a humble custodian now.
这样的表通常需要送去瑞士修半年
A piece like this will often have to go to Switzerland for six months.
也就是说 我现在手里有
So I have this funny bit about how,
关于董事会特别委员会
for the special committee of the board,
以及这个负责调查的律所的搞笑段子
and the... the white shoe firm that will handle the investigation,
我父亲是如何施压 雇了一间可以替他们遮掩的公司
how my dad's putting pressure to hire a firm that will help them cover up.
-你有听到什么吗  -有啊
- Do you hear anything? - Yeah.
有点像是在替他们遮掩
So it's, it's like, cover-up.
收拾烂摊子 就像是玩具反斗城
Cover-up our ass. Like Toys 'R' Us.
-收拾烂摊子  -对耶
- Cover-up our ass. - Yeah.
-不是吗  -我不知道
- No? - I don't know.
-不是  -但我认为"爱之船"的视频还不错
- No. - But I think that the Love Boat vids are good.
是啊 爱之船
Yeah, Love Boat.
由于我们紧急抽时间给你们录影
Hey! Because we pushed taping for you,
所以我们还在召集观众
we're still filling up the audience.
-但不会耽搁太长时间  -很好
- But shouldn't be too long. - Cool.
-你们需要些什么吗  -不用了 谢谢
- Do you guys need anything? - We're great. Thank you.
-你还好吗  -是的 我很好
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I'm good. Yeah.
-他正在给他隐形的朋友打飞机  -没有
- He's just jerking off his invisible friend. - No.
对了 编剧在哪
Hey, so, where are the writers at?
-通常编剧和嘉宾都...  -不 你说的是通常
- Um, generally writers and guests are... - Oh, no, generally,
但我认识一个"讽刺文社"的人  他认识迪伦
but I knew a guy at the Lampoon who knows Dylan.
我能找下他们 打声招呼吗
Can I just find them to say hi?
我或许可以给这些大师提供些素材
I might pitch a couple of areas for the gigglebots?
我们时间真的不太够
Oh, well, we don't really have time.
-我们差不多要上台了  -没事的 我去找他们
- We gotta kind of get up there. - It's cool, I'll find him.
来啦 小罗 你好吗
Hey, Rome, how you doing?
我刚刚在电视上激情讲述 我和爸爸外出捕杀鳟鱼
I've just been on TV waxing lyrical about me and dad out murdering trout
还有在旧的棉花糖洞附近唱船夫号子的事
and singing sea shanties around the old marshmallow hole.
-你看过了吗  -我刚才劝退了爸
- Have you read this thing? - Now, I talked dad down.
他想让我们所有人上一档脱口秀
He wanted us all to appear on a talk show.
别逗了
Get the fuck out of here.
一起坐在沙发上 我觉得好傻
Sitting on a couch together I thought would be very gauche.
所以我起草了这个 来开启并结束这次讨论
So I drafted this to land and to end debate.
他想让我们所有人都签个名
He wants us all to sign it.
好家伙 这可真是大杂烩
Man, this is quite a rich brew.
我觉得一封正式的回应 可以让我们划清界限
Well, I think a formal response really draws a line under it.
我想大家一定都在问你们
I'm sure you're being asked,
所以这封回应算是我们清楚表明
so this is just us very clearly saying
我们不掺合肯德尔的事情
that we're not a part of Kendall's thing.
怎么 你们得承认这写得非常精准了
What? You would have to say it's accurate.
是啊 就像奥斯瓦尔德一样精准
Yeah, accurate like Oswald was accurate.
[刺杀美国前总统肯尼迪的凶手]
我希望我们都签字 然后今晚发布给媒体
I want us all to sign it for release to media tonight.
我想说 这... 这有点像地狱寄来的贺卡
I mean, it's kind of It's kind of a greeting card from hell.
-什么  -这是用新罗马字体写的处决信
- What? - It's a Times New Roman firing squad.
没错  这挺可怕的
Yeah, it's pretty horrible, you know?
好吧 内容基本上都确认过了...
Well. It's all basically verified so...
是啊 瘾君子 谎话连篇 失职的父亲
Well, yeah, drug addict, serial liar, absentee father,
他那些与各种女人不正当关系的历史
history of his own problematic relations with women.
-哪一条说得不对  -不 说得很对
- Which of those isn't true? - No. It's accurate, you know.
但这会公诸于世 可能永远流传
But this would be out there, like, forever.
你知道吗 只要PGN想让我看着不靠谱
You know, PGN pulls up that photo of me with the pony tail
他们就会发那张我扎马尾辫的照片
anytime they wanna make me look untrustworthy.
好吧 听我说 肯德尔使命必达
Okay. Look, Kendall is on a mission.
除非我们整垮他 他绝不会善罢甘休
And he's not going to stop unless we take his legs out.
爸希望我们所有人都这么做吗
And did dad want for all of us to do this?
如果是我们三人签名的话 就更有说服力
It's more powerful if it comes from all three of us.
-你满口胡言  -什么
- Now, you're full of shit. - What?
-我... 我不会签字的  -罗曼 为什么
- I'm... I'm not signing this. - Roman, why not?
因为我不想签 这让我不舒服
Because I don't want to. It makes me feel unwell.
他教会我怎样在厕所小便的时候瞄准
He taught me how to aim my peepee in the toilet.
什么鬼 这不是理由 罗曼
The fuck? That's not a reason, Roman.
那把我送上理由的法庭 告我吧
Take me to reason court and fucking sue me.
罗曼 我们有时都得做些不得已的事
Roman, we all have to do things we don't want to sometimes.
我不会做的 这不是对我最有利的事 所以我不做
I just don't. This is not in my best interest, so, no.
-康纳  -我不想显得矫情
- Connor? - Well, I don't wanna be a bitch.
但我的签名价值连城
But my signature is valuable
我不会随随便便就签了
real estate and I'm not giving it away for free.
好吧 你想要什么
Okay. What do you want?
我需要考虑一下
I would like some consideration.
我想要一些跪舔[来点好处]
I would like some suck, suck on my dicky-dick.
-我的天哪  -我也是
- Oh, my God. - Same.
我现在觉得自己没被跪舔好
I'm feeling brutally un-suck-sucked right now.
你们这两个巨婴
You're babies.
请把我的名字撤掉
Take my name off, please.
行吧 我自己签
Fine. I'll do it myself.
感谢你们一如既往的帮助
Thanks all the fucking help as always.
很高兴今晚在这里见到这么多人
Um, it's so good to see so many of you here to tonight.
我们优秀的广告商们
Our amazing advertisers, and,
没有你们的话 就不会有我们
you know, we'd be nothing without you.
我只想对你们所有人说
And I just wanna say to you all
无论上面正在发生些什么
whatever is happening up in the clouds,
可能是诸神乱战
where the gods play a little rough and tumble,
在这里 还是一切照旧
down here, it is very much, business as usual.
所以敬你们 祝平安度过此次风暴
So here's to you, here's to weathering the storm.
没错 这... 这更贴近...
Yeah, like that's... that's closer to the idea...
你们在这
Here they are.
奋斗的天才精英们 轰隆 轰隆[火车车轮声]
The geniuses at work! Clickity- clack, clickity-clack.
-你好啊  -是迪伦吗
- Okay. Hello. - Dylan?
-是我  -你好 我认识在"讽刺文社"上班的帕特
- Yeah? - Yeah, hey, I I knew Pat at the Lampoon.
-这样啊  -他说你超级搞笑
- Oh, okay. - He says you're like a super funny dude.
-好吧  -不 你的确是
- Oh, well - Yeah. No, you are.
我只是想顺道过来跟你们说
I just wanted to drop by and let you guys know
你们真的很棒 非常聪明 很有讽刺精神
you do awesome work, very smart, very satirical.
-谢谢 伙计  -不客气
- Cool. Thanks, man. - Yeah, yeah.
-听我说 我希望你们来喷我  -好的
- Hey, listen, I want you guys to hit me. - Yes.
对我俄狄孬种绝不要留情
Just Rickles the fuck out of Oedipussy here?
-我能受得住  -这只是表演 所以...
- I can take it. - Well, it's just the show so...
-太对了 只是表演  -你懂的
- Yeah, yeah. It's the show. - You know.
肯 能耽误你几秒钟吗
Hey. Ken, can I grab for a second?
这几位是编剧
Hey. These are the writers.
-你们好  -迪伦 伙计 喷死我吧
- Hi. - Dylan, my man. Hurt me.
-肯 肯 走吧  -让我不能翻身
- Ken. Ken. Please. - Fucking hurt me.
天哪
Jesus Christ.
-怎么了  -我还不确定这个传播得有多广
- What's up? - I'm not sure how wide this has gone,
-我才刚看到 可是...  -好
- I'm just seeing it now. But... - Okay.
你该...
You should...
所以... 这样啊
So... okay.
所以...
So...
我... 我们该怎么办
So... What... what do I... What do we do with this?
我觉得这其实不算是什么事儿
Because this is actually really sort of nothing, I think.
-对不对  -我觉得这算事儿吧
- Yeah? - No, I wouldn't say it's nothing.
冷酷无情啊
That's below the belt.
全世界都看得到吗 还是只有我们
Is the world seeing this or or just basically us?
是的 全世界
Yeah, the whole world.
我们能让他们今晚别用吗 他们会提到吗
Can we ask them not to use it tonight? Will they mention it?
我觉得他们很有可能会提到
I think they'll probably mention it.
但这是很私人的事情 我感觉...
But they but it's private, I feel like...
对 可是已经公开了
Yeah. But it's not private.
-公开了  -对
- No. - No. Okay.
我还是可以上台吧 我应该上的吧 对吧
I mean, can I still go on? I feel like I still go on, right?
-我知道 我觉得没事吧  -对
- Yeah, I know. I think it's fine. - Yeah.
我们应该能避开这个话题吧
It's just the kind of thing where we just maybe steer away from it.
-也许可以...  -往里走走
- You know? Maybe... - Here, here.
-对 我担心的是...  -对
- Right. So, my concern is that it might... - Yeah.
-不提的话反而会很奇怪  -好吧
- It might be weird if we don't mention it. - Sure.
-那行  -好
- Absolutely. - Okay. Good.
你能到场真是慷慨
Look, it is big of you to come here.
-我们想待你公平  -没问题 我很配合
- We wanna be fair. - Totally. And I'm game.
-好 那就好  -好
- Okay. That's great. - Yeah.
只是由于一些法律问题
There's just a you know, a possibility with all the legal of it
我可能不得不退出 但不伤和气吧
that I might have to bow out, but we're good.
-应该没事吧  -这样
- We're good. - Right.
可是我们十五分钟后就要开录了
We tape in 15 minutes.
我知道 我可以帮助解决这个问题
Sure, no, and I'd help with that. Obviously.
那你要怎么帮呢
Right. How would you help with that?
我有关系
I know people.
你... 要干嘛 打给Jay-Z然后叫他...
You... You're gonna what? Call Jay-Z and get him to...
-当然  -十五分钟后来录节目吗
- Yeah. A name. - to do the show in 15 minutes?
-我可以的  -不用
- I can do that. - No, no.
我觉得你有点想多了
I think you're over-thinking this.
我们是表演喜剧的 节目得有趣
It's a comedy show. We're gonna we're gonna have fun.
索菲虽然很难缠 但她很公正
And Sophie is tough, but she's fair.
你是我们的嘉宾
Look, and you're our guest.
-所以...  -我知道 你说得对
- So... - No, I know. You're right.
-所以没事了吗  -当然没事了
- Yeah. So we're... we're good? - Okay. Yeah, no, for sure.
-好  -很好
- Okay. - Okay.
很好
Great.
你来了
Hey!
来了
Hey.
你来干吗
What are you in for?
我吗 我只是来跟格丽看些数据
Ah, me? Just running some numbers with Gerri on you know,
就是那该死的分销协议
the fucking getting the distribution deals for these
这根本就是谋杀
Fucking... It's murder.
-乖儿子  -是是是
- Good kid. - Yeah. Uh-huh.
抱歉我没签那封信 我...
Um, but sorry about the letter or whatever, I just...
你不想卷进来吧
Keeping your nose out, huh?
我不知道 应该吧
Well, I don't know, I guess.
挺精明的嘛
Smart cookie, huh?
-精明能干的小伙  -你也知道
- Smart little fucking cookie, hey? - Well, you know?
我看过你的采访了
I, saw your little interview.
那个啊 别细究了
Oh, right. Yeah, we don't have to dissect that.
"我爱我爸爸"
"Ooo, I wuv my daddy".
-好吧  -我从来没想过你是个死玻璃
- Yeah. - I never figured you for a faggot.
-开个玩笑 玩笑而已  -我听得出来
- I'm kidding. I'm kidding. - I know, I know.
那次钓鱼是怎么回事 我没印象了
So what's this, uh fishing thing? I don't remember.
其实是康纳来着 康纳带我去的
Oh, yeah, that was, Connor, actually. Connor took me on that.
开心的童年回忆可以反复回味
But, you know, single multi-use happy childhood memory. So yeah.
我的天啊 真是坏消息呢
"Oh, my God. Such sad news.
你们猜怎么着 我们的嘉宾跑路了
Guess what, we're down a guest.
俄狄孬种放我鸽子
Oedipussy has ghosted my ass.
我简直伤心欲绝
Yeah. And I'm like heartbroken,
我给他起了那么多外号要叫他
because I had so many names I was going to call him.
恍然大悟·罗伊科
Wokestar Royco.
好蠢货·阿诺德[叛徒] 偏执狂肯德尔
Benedickhead Arnold, Paranoid Kendroid.
但是老实说 没有什么能比得上
But honestly, nothing could be as
他亲妹妹发表的公开信那般残暴
brutal as the open letter his own sister released.
我非常关心我哥哥的健康
I am deeply concerned for the wellbeing of my brother.
整个家族一直都在支持他通过各种尝试
Our entire family has supported him through his many attempts
戒掉他的各种瘾
At rehabilitation for his multiple addictions.
但是过去几天的事情足以证明
But the events of the last days have made it clear
我们对他能康复所抱的希望是错误的
That our hopes for his recovery were misplaced.
他曾对我咆哮着发表过厌女言论
I've now been a direct witness to his misogynistic rants
还把我与一些历史伟人作比较
and comparisons to world historical figures
这些都展现了他浮夸且混乱的思想
that were suggestive of grandiose and disordered thinking.
我想请求各位 能在这艰难的时刻
And I would ask that people give my brother privacy and consideration
给予我的哥哥一些私人空间和关怀
during this difficult time.
这还是从他妹妹嘴里说出来的 她可是个好人"
And that's from his sister and she's the fucking nice one."
-联邦调查局到楼下了  -什么
- The FBI is downstairs. - What?
-对  -叫他们滚蛋
- Yeah. - Tell them to fuck off.
这些是不会滚的联邦调查局
Yeah, these are the ones who don't fuck off.
-这是搜查令  -前台在做什么
- This is a search warrant. - What do they do at the front desk?
我们该怎么办 他们在门口了
What are we doing? They're at the gates.
-我们能打给南区吗  -可以
- Can we call Southern district? - Okay.
-去找莱欧 快快快  -好的好的
- Get Layo, get, get, get, get, get. - Okay, okay.
能拖延时间吗 我要不要打给米歇尔·安
Can we stall 'em? Shall I call Michelle-Anne?
不行 我想司法部副部长
No, I think that the Deputy Attorney
被你联系米歇尔·安的举动惊动了
General got spooked by you talking to Michelle-Anne.
那米歇尔·安他娘的做了什么 她一点都不敏锐
Well, what the fuck did Michelle-Anne do? She's got no fucking acumen.
我猜政府不是佩兹糖果盒
Well, I guess the Government isn't a fucking Pez dispenser.
按个按钮就能有东西跳出来
You don't push a button and something pops out the other end.
-不必解释 我很清楚  -下面得有二十来个人
- Yes, I am well-aware. - There's about 20 of them down there.
何不请他们明天再来
Why don't we just ask them if they can come back tomorrow?
罗根 他们要上来了
Logan, they are coming up,
不开门的话他们一定会破门而入
and if you don't open the door, they will kick it in.
不打开档案柜的话 他们就会掏出撬棍
And if you don't open the filing cabinet, they will pull out a crow bar.
这已经展现了他们的决心 媒体都就位了
This is a show of resolve and there are cameras outside
他们不能看到我们阻挠联邦调查局
and they do not need to see the FBI meeting any resistance.
我们怎么办
What do we say?
配合调查
Cooperate.
-开门 让他们进来吧  -走走走
- Open up. Let them in. - Come on. Let's go.
好 我给楼下打电话
Okay. I will call down and I'll ask
跟负责的特工说说 我们想点办法
to talk to the lead agent and we will work something out.
-好  -确定配合调查
- Okay. - We're cooperating?
确定
We're cooperating.
叫来特别委员会 把律师也叫来
Get the special committee, shift the legals.
我们要配合工作
We're cooperating.
人们收看我们频道太久了 我们得让标志动起来
People watch our channel for so long, we had to animate our logo
不然这个标志就快烧穿他们的屏幕了
because it was burning into people's screens.
我们的观众就是这么忠诚
I mean, that is how loyal the viewers are.
我们一定会挺过这个小插曲
And you know, we will survive this whole episode
因为我们有能力
because... Because of our strength,
我们有才华 我们有价值
because of our depth of talent, and because of our values.
我们有真正的价值 什么事
Our true values. Yes?
伙伴们 有件事要提醒大家
Um, guys, just a little heads-up.
这不是大事
And this is not something I want us to get out
我不想因为此事场面失控而毁了今晚
of proportion or spoil the evening,
但似乎有些联邦调查局的贵宾
but it would that seem some agents of Federal law enforcement
正在突袭调查大楼
are raiding the premises right now.
如果大家有看到的话 也就是这么回事了
So if you see them, that's what that is.
不用收拾了 放着就行
It's fine. It's fine. Just fucking leave it.
大家可以看到 联邦调查局正在
"As you can see, the FBI is currently
突袭调查位于曼哈顿下城区的韦斯达总部
raiding Waystar headquarters in lower Manhattan."
旨在调查...
"In order to execute an..."